穆斯女神 不管你从哪里得知 告诉我（他们的事）吧
这没什么 只是被猫抓伤了而已
It's nothing. It's just a cat scratch.
又不是一次两次了
I've had a million of 'em.
我才不要为了这点伤就去看医生
I'm not going to the doctor for a cat scratch.
你可能会有危险
Your life could be in danger.
Nick 这怎么可能
Nick, that's ridiculous.
- 你不了解她   - 她是什么人
- You don't understand what she is. - What is she?
她是个有魅力 成功的女人
She's an attractive, successful woman.
你曾经救过她的命
You saved her life once.
你怎么突然这么针对她
What do you suddenly have against her now?
你有什么瞒着我
And what aren't you telling me?
难道你跟她之间发生了什么
Did you have some sort of a relationship with her?
- 没有  - 那这到底是怎么回事
- No. - Then what is it?
她是个女巫 好吧
She's a witch, okay?
你不知道到底发生了什么
You don't know what's going on here.
你得去看医生
You're going to the doctor.
早上好
Morning.
你已经去过商店了
You went shopping already?
是的 Shemanski公园的露天市场
You bet. Shemanski park outdoor market.
吃货会在早上市场开门时
The true epicure always does his shopping
去选好东西
while the farmers set up.
嗨 今晚你在哪儿吃饭
Hey, what are you doing for dinner?
看工作情况了 怎么了
That depends on work. Why?
我买了一级棒的素牛排
Well, I scored these primo veggie steaks.
如果你来 我就多化一块肉
If I know when you're coming, I'll defrost an extra.
- 素牛排  - 很美味的
- Veggie steaks? - They're excellent.
你知道的 再加上一点柑橘酢 零残忍
You know, a little ponzu? Cruelty-free.
零残忍 是一种对于素食者的素食行为的定义
我怎能对这样的美味说不
How can I say "No" To that?
- 好  - Hank 你回来了
- All right. - Hank, you back?
恩 我马上出发
Yeah. I'm leaving now.
我在Fuller咖啡店等你
I'll meet you at Fuller's coffee shop.
好的
Great.
我很期待你的素牛排哦
Hey, I cannot wait for those veggie steaks.
八点准时回来
8：00 sharp.
哇哦 你这是闹哪儿样啊
Okay. So what happened to you?
在考爱岛高空滑索
Ziplining in Kauai.
着陆的时候有点激动过头 伤了跟腱
Landed a little too enthusiastically and tore my achilles.
真要命 那医生怎么说
Man what'd the doctor say?
事实上 他坚持让我休息
Actually, he was very adamant.
"让你搭档把所有活都做了"
"Let your partner do all the work."
就好像现在不是这样似的
As if I don't already.
所以你一个人去索道滑行
So you were zip-lining alone?
这个嘛 还真不是
Well, not exactly.
- 你记得Nadine吗  - 你前妻
- You remember Nadine? - Ex-wife Nadine?
恩 我带她一起去的
Yeah. I took her.
- 就想试试  - 唔
- It was kind of an experiment. - Whew.
我们仍然有很多共同之处
You know, we still have a lot in common.
我倒没看出来
I didn't see that one coming.
恩 我知道 我也没看出来
Yeah, I know. Neither did I.
我不在的时候发生了什么
Um, so what'd I miss?
跟往常没什么区别 有恶魔 还有些外星人
The usual.The devil. A couple of space aliens.
是啊
Yeah.
这可不是回火产生的暴击声
I don't think that was a backfire.
不是 你去看看 我呼叫支援
No. You go. I'll call it in.
警察 让我过去
Police! Let me through!
快走
Move!
- 你是爱我的  - Anton 让我离开
- You love me. - Let go, Anton!
Khloe 我们必须马上离开这里
Khloe, we have to get out of here now.
就是现在 宝贝快来
Now! Come on, baby.
Anton 求你了
Anton, please.
Khloe 你是我的人
You're mine, Khloe.
不 Anton 放开我
No! Anton, let go of me!
放开她
Let her go!
快走
Get out!
Khloe
Khloe!
我是Burkhardt 我在Nolen书店追赶一名持枪嫌犯
This is Burkhardt, I'm in foot pursuit of an armed suspect at Nolen's books
在西北第一大街与戴维斯街分界处
on Northwest First and Davis.
听说嫌犯跳进河里了
Heard the suspect took a dive into the river.
是啊
Yeah
- 活着还是死了  - 不知道
- Alive or dead? - I don't know.
但是如果他浮上来了 肯定是在我看不到的地方
But if he came up, it was not where I could see it.
你看到他了
Well, you have that look.
- 他是格林生物  - 所以他能够待在水下
- He's wesen. - So he could've stayed under.
也许吧
Maybe.
潜水员们正在搜寻
Divers are searching now.
这个是受害者 Evan Childs
So this is the vic? Evan Childs?
是 他是个作家 这次是他的签售活动
Yeah, he was the writer. It was his book signing.
那个女孩儿呢 我看她认识开枪的人
What about the girl? I think she knew the shooter.
确实
She does.
据她所说 我是指Khloe Sedgwick
According to her, and by "Her" I mean. Khloe Sedgwick
30岁 死者的女朋友
age 30, girlfriend of the vic.
她说开枪的人名为Anton Cole
She said the shooter's name is Anton Cole.
我们正在找他的住址
We're running down his place of residence.
她有说怎么和他认识的吗
She say how she knew him?
这个嘛 他是她的前男友
Well, he's an ex-boyfriend.
这是宗冲动犯罪
So we're talking crime of passion.
- 我猜是  - 好吧
- That'd be my guess. - All right.
我们来跟她谈谈
Let's talk to her.
跟我走
Follow me.
你认识Anton Cole有多长时间了
How long have you known Anton Cole?
两年多一点
Uh, a little over two years.
六个月前我们分手了
We... we broke up about six months ago.
那个时候你认识了Childs先生
That's when you started seeing Mr. Childs?
恩 算是吧
Yeah, I guess.
那时候你同时在和他们两个约会嘛
Were you seeing both at the same time?
不 我不会这样做的
No, I don't do that.
Anton 他只是 他无法释怀
Anton, he just... he wouldn't let go.
他一直打来电话 想让我们复合
He kept calling and wanting to get back together.
之后 Evan开始变得很烦躁
And then, Evan started getting pretty upset.
再之后 Anton开始出现在我家周围
And then Anton started showing up at my house
说Evan配不上我
saying that Evan wasn't good enough for me,
而他才是我的真命天子
but that he was.
你把这些跟警察局备案了吗
And did you report any of this to the police?
你们不明白
You don't understand.
不如你跟我们讲讲
Why don't you tell us?
这听起来挺吓人的
This is gonna sound pretty terrible,
但是男人们很容易为我倾倒
but guys fall for me pretty easily.
当他们爱上我的时候 他们就 他们就难以停下来
And when they do, they just... they don't stop,
之后事情会变得令人难以忍受
and it can get really oppressive.
我 我不是故意表现的很自负
I-I don't mean to sound conceited.
这就是事实
It's just the way that it is.
如果不是你的话
If it hadn't have been for you...
他很可能杀了我
He would've killed me.
谢谢
Thank you.
你会没事儿的
You're gonna be okay.
但你们还没有找到他
But you haven't found him yet.
这个嘛 还没有 但是我们会派一名警官守在你家门前 直到我们找到凶手
Well, not yet, but we'll put an officer in front of your house until we do.
如果他跟你联系 打电话通知我
If he contacts you, call me.
我看你是不会洗手了
Are you going to wash that hand?
瞎说啥呢啊
What are you talking about?
饶了我吧
Give me a break.
嗨 找到Anton的住址了 东南部的一栋阁楼
Hey, got a 20 on Anton's place of residence, a loft in the Southeast.
他风度翩翩并且才华横溢
He was such a gentle soul and so talented.
和他女朋友分手让他有些崩溃
He broke up with his girlfriend, and it kinda tore him up.
在那之后他有些自闭
And, well, he kept to himself after that.
当他过来的时候 他一般都说些什么
And when he would come over, what would you talk about?
大多关于他的艺术和Khloe 就是他的女朋友
Mostly about his art and Khloe, his girlfriend.
他说她是他灵感的源泉
He said she was his inspiration.
我觉得说的太浪漫了
I thought that was very romantic.
但个人认为 我觉得他说的太夸张了
But personally, I think he gave her way too much credit.
但那就是爱 不是吗
But I guess that's love, right?
好吧 多谢你的帮忙 现在我们就四处看看
Well, thank you for your help. We'll take a look around now.
好 如果需要记得打给我 我就在楼下
Well, call me if you need me. I'll be downstairs.
搜索队刚刚回报
Search team just reported in.
没有找到Anton的尸体
Anton's body has not been found.
没准儿他往下游走了
Doesn't mean he's not way downriver.
- 但是  - 这个"但是"吓到我了
- But... - It's the "But" That scares me.
安全
Clear!
依我所见 这个男人看起来
In my humble opinion, it seems this guy
陷入到某种痴迷当中
was sort of obsessed
没准儿有点疯狂地迷恋着Sedgwick小姐
and maybe a little out of his mind with Ms. Sedgwick.
你这么想
You think?
有趣的是 他的风格似乎从印象派变成了神经病流派
Interestingly, his style seems to range from impressionistic to "WTF."
你们得来看看这个
Better take a look at this.
有预谋的冲动犯罪
A pre-illustrated crime of passion.
我猜这个可以证明了这是有预谋的
I guess that proves premeditation.
- Juliette  - Nick
- Juliette. - Nick!
太好了你接电话了
I'm glad I got you.
恩 我正在查案
Yeah, I'm in the middle of an investigation.
喔 不好意思 就占用你一会儿时间
Oh. I'm sorry. This'll really just take a second.
看 我 我知道这个也许有些莫名其妙
Look, I-I know this might seem a little bit out of nowhere,
但今晚你能过来和我一起吃个饭吗
but could you come over for dinner tonight?
恩 好的 出了什么事儿吗
Yeah, sure. Is there a problem?
没有 什么事儿也没有
No, not... not at all.
我只是觉得 如果我们能谈谈的话是很好的
I just thought it would be nice if we could talk.
恩 什么时候
Okay. What time?
- 大约八点钟  - 好的
- Around 8:00? - All right.
八点见
8:00. I'll see you then.
好 等会儿见
Great. I will see you then.
你和Juliette有事情
You doing something with Juliette?
恩 我们要一起吃个晚饭
Yeah, I guess we're having dinner.
怎么 情况变得越来越好了
What, things are getting better?
我完全不知道
If they are, nobody told me.
Nick 走吧
Nick.
Nick
- 嗯  - 我们走吧
- Yeah? - Let's go.
今天要去做物理治疗
I got a date with physical therapy.
稍后我再和你联系
I'll check with you after.
那个是Anton
Is that Anton?
恩
Yeah.
我没太看清他
I didn't get a very good look at him,
但是这已经相当接近他跑之前我所看的样子了
but this is pretty much what I saw before he ran.
恩 真希望我们能把它贴到全境通告上
Yeah, wish we could put that on an APB.
我不知道有没有用
I'm not sure that would help.
替我向Juliette问好
Say hi to Juliette.
祝你晚饭吃的顺利
Hope dinner goes well.
恩 我也想
Yeah, me too.
嗨 警探
Hey, Detective.
- 有什么情况吗  - 没有
- Any problems? - No.
她在里边 没有人进入 也没有人出来
She's inside. Nobody in, nobody out.
- 谁  - 我是Burkhardt警探
- Who is it? - It's Detective Burkhardt.
没事儿 你可以打开门
It's okay. You can open the door.
不好意思打扰你
Sorry to bother you.
只是需要做些后续调查
Just needed to do a little follow-up.
进来吧
Come on in.
让我先穿上些衣服
Let me just go put some clothes on.
- 晚上好  - 嗨 Monroe 我是Juliette
- Good evening. - Hey, Monroe, it's Juliette.
Juliette 你还好吗
Juliette! How are ya?
相当好 正在做晚餐
Pretty good. Just making a little dinner.
真巧 我也是
Yeah, me too.
听着 我打电话的目的是想在Nick来之前跟你聊一聊
Listen, the reason I'm calling is I wanted to talk to you before Nick got here.
Nick要去你那儿
Nick's coming over to your place?
- 是啊 我正在做晚饭  - 等会儿
- Yeah, I'm making his dinner. - Hold on.
你正在做你们俩的晚饭
You're making dinner for you and Nick?
是的
Yeah.
我 你知道的 我想要跟他谈谈
I, you know, I wanted to talk to him
关于最近发生的一些事情
about some of the things that have been happening lately.
我觉得晚饭会是
And I thought dinner would be...
那不是很重要
well, that's not important.
但在他到之前
But before he gets here, I...
我只想知道他是否跟你谈过我们之间的关系
I just wanted to know if he has said anything to you about our relationship or...
- 你和我  - 不 我和Nick之间的关系
- Yours and mine? - No, me and Nick.
我只是 我只是有点紧张
I'm just a... I'm a little nervous.
我希望能知道他是怎么想的
I wish I knew how he felt.
这个嘛 他一直在盼着这样的事情发生
Well, he's been waiting for something like this for kind of a long time.
所以我猜你只好
So I guess you're just gonna have to, you know,
静下心来 看看接下来会发生什么
get into it and see where it goes.
恩 你是对的 你是对的
Yeah, you're right. You're right.
多谢 这正是我需要听到的话
Thank you... that's exactly what I needed to hear.
- 多谢了 Monroe  - 祝你好运
- Thanks, Monroe. - Good luck.
多谢 拜
Thanks. Bye.
不好意思让你久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.
你想跟我谈些什么
What was it you wanted to talk to me about?
我们还没有找到Anton
We haven't found Anton yet.
那他还活着
Then he's still alive.
我们必须假定这种情况继续追查下去
We have to proceed as if he is.
你不必亲自过来通知我
You didn't have to come all the way here to tell me that...
你本可以就打个电话
you could've just called.
我不是为这事儿才来的
That's not why I'm here.
你以前看过这个吗
You ever seen this?
呃 没有
Uh, no.
那是Anton的作品 我知道的
That's Anton's work. I know that.
看起来Anton已经计划很久了
It seems as though Anton has been planning this for a long time.
我们在他的阁楼里找到的
We found this in his loft.
你上次去那里是什么时候
When was the last time you were there?
几个月前
Couple of months ago.
他为你画了许多张画
You were the subject of a number of his paintings.
- 你做他的模特  - 是的
- Do you model for him? - Yes.
但是我也为其他人做过
But I've done that for others.
要不这些艺术品是怎么来的
That's how I get all this artwork.
我可负担不起
I never could've afforded it otherwise.
所以你迷恋艺术家
So you have a thing for artists?
我只是迷恋那些视野独特的人
I have a thing for people who see the world differently.
我启发他们
I inspire them.
是吗 怎么启发
Yeah? How?
这很难用语言来言明
It's kind of hard to explain.
你可以试着解释看看
Well, why don't you try?
好吧
Okay.
就是这么开始的
That's how it starts,
但不是这样结束的
but it's never how it ends.
就那么 发生了些事情
It's just... Something that happens.
是不可抑制的
It's not something that can be controlled.
也是不该被抑制的
It's not something that should be controlled.
我从没勉强过他们
I never force myself on them.
他们想要我 也需要我
They want me, And they need me.
可是却总没有善终
That doesn't always end well.
嗯 很多伟大的艺术家都英年早逝 而且有暴力倾向 近乎疯狂
Mm, a lot of the great artists died young and violently, half-mad.
但我想他们任何一个人也不会想用盛名来换取完整而乏味的一生
But I doubt that any of them would trade their fame for banality and a longer life.
那你怎么来做出选择
So how do you choose them?
我想是靠天赋
I guess it's a talent,
内心的驱使 激情
a drive, passion,
就像我从你身上感受到的一样
like what I sense in you.
我不是个艺术家
I'm not an artist.
也许只是你还没发现罢了
Maybe you just don't know it yet.
你浑身散发着某种强大的力量
There's something that's just deeply powerful about you.
我不知道那是什么 但我被深深的吸引住了
I don't know what it is, but I'm drawn to it.
你怕了吗
Does that scare you?
- 应该如此吗  - 只有你能回答
- Should it? - Only you can answer that.
什么让你感到害怕
What scares you?
你留下后可能发生的事
What might happen if you stay.
我不该这么做
I shouldn't have done that.
- 我不会伤害你的  - 我知道你是什么
- I'm not gonna hurt you. - I know what you are.
听着 这只是个错误 好吗
Look, it was a mistake, okay?
- 你得赶紧离开  - Khloe 我是来帮你的
- You need to go. - Khloe, I'm here to help you.
你不用感到害怕
You don't have to be afraid of me.
我是Burkhardt
Burkhardt.
你要和Juliette一起吃晚饭
So you're having dinner with Juliette?
- Monroe  - 是的
- Monroe? - Yep.
两块解冻的高级素牛排
With two defrosted primo veggie steaks.
想起什么了吗
Ring a dinner bell?
喔 天哪
Oh, my God.
我该去Juliette那儿的
I'm supposed to be at Juliette's.
恩 她打过电话了
Yeah. She called.
那时我就开始怀疑你不会来了
That's when I began to suspect you might not be showing up,
除非你计划吃两顿晚饭
unless you're planning on having two dinners tonight.
我正在查案
I'm in the middle of an investigation right now.
- 我会给你打回去的  - 好吧
- I'll call you back. -  All right.
我得走了
I have to go.
我走之后锁好门
Lock the door behind me.
对不起 我迟到了
Sorry, I'm late.
我正有些担心呢
I was getting a little worried,
我想也许你改主意了
I thought maybe you changed your mind.
没有 只是被一件案子拖住了
No, just got held up on a case.
没事儿 嗯 你来了我就很高兴了
That's okay. Um, I'm just glad you're here.
快进来
Come in.
这地方看着不错
The place looks great.
我什么都没有动过
I didn't change anything.
晚饭有点凉了
Um, look, dinner's a little cold,
我去加热一下
so why don't I warm it up?
那么
So...
你想跟我谈什么
What did you want to talk to me about?
喔 直奔主题 好
Oh. Right to the point. Okay.
呃 我想也应该开门见山
Um, I guess no reason not to.
如果要不是你的话
If it hadn't been for you...
我的记忆越来越清晰了
Well, things are starting to get clearer for me.
"清晰" 也许不是最合适的词 不管了
"Clearer" Might not be the best word for it, whatever it is.
我知道我这几个礼拜对你很不好
You know, I know that I've been treating you unfairly these last few weeks,
我只想说声抱歉
and I just want to say I'm sorry.
Nick
Nick?
我猜是天赋
I guess it's a talent,
内心的驱使 激情
a drive, a passion.
- 就像我从你身上感受到的一样  - Nick 怎么了
- Like what I sense in you... - Nick?
啊
Yeah?
我正试着道歉
I'm trying to apologize.
为什么
For what?
为之前我们之间发生的那些事
For how things have been going between us,
还有 为我对你的方式道歉
and... How I've been treating you.
我想我可能是疯了
I thought I was losing my mind.
无论从哪点来看 我绝对是不太正常
You know, for all intents and purposes, I was losing my mind.
但也许这点儿代价是值得的
But maybe that's what it took,
因为关于你的记忆我开始想起来了
because my memories of you are coming back.
Nick
Nick.
- 也许不完整  - Nick
- Maybe not neatly... - Nick.
也没有逻辑性 但是我想让你知道 我开始记起你了
Or logically, but I do want you to know that I'm starting to remember you
还有那些我们做过的事儿以及我的感觉
and things that we did together and things I felt.
听着 我知道这很
Look, I-I know it's a lot of...
在我们经历过这么多事情之后
after everything we've been through...
对我来说真的太多了
Really a lot for me.
你难道不想说些什么吗
Don't you want to say anything?
Nick
Nick.
你听到我刚才说什么了吗
Did you hear what I just said?
不好意思 什么
I'm sorry. What?
听着 今晚我觉得有点累了
Look, I-I'm feeling a little off tonight.
我想 工作可能有点让我烦心了
I, uh, think work might be starting to get to me a little.
好 也许这不是个好时候
Okay, m-maybe this just wasn't a good time.
恩 也许你是对的
Yeah, you're probably right.
谢谢你理解
Thanks.
我们之后再谈吧
Let's talk soon.
Nick
Nick?
你已经回来了
You home already?
- 是的  - 喔 老兄
- Yeah. - Oh, man.
你可别是为了第二顿晚饭才回来这么早
I hope you didn't come for a second dinner.
我只是在开玩笑
You know, I was just joking about that.
我 呃 我把两块素牛排都吃了
And I, um... I kinda ate both veggie steaks.
进行的如何
So how'd it go?
我是说 她说得好像这顿饭挺重要似的
I mean, she made it sound like this is gonna be sort of an important dinner.
- 我们没有吃成  - 怎么这样
- We didn't eat. - Ooh.
你为了吃晚饭去了她家 但你们却没吃
You went over to her house for dinner, and you didn't eat.
你们一定谈了好多吧
You must've had a lot to talk about.
那倒没有
Not really.
好吧 我只想说 "怎么会"
Well, let me just say, "Huh."
这本该是个重要的时刻
It was supposed to be the big moment, you know?
她记起了你
She's remembering you.
她邀请你去谈一谈
She invites you over to talk.
你想要怎样
Wha... What do you want?
这跟我想要什么没关系
It's not about me wanting anything.
- 我只是试着去 就是 去支持你  - 为什么
- I'm just trying to be, you know, supportive. - Why?
我是说 我的个人生活对你来说这么有趣吗
I mean, does my personal life interest you that much?
你再说一遍
Excuse me?
听着 我们没吃饭 也没谈什么
Look...We didn't eat, and we didn't talk.
你还需要知道什么
What more do you need to know?
我不需要知道任何事
I don't need to know anything
除了为什么你今天这个样子
except why are you acting like this?
听着 我不明白你说什么
Look, I don't understand this.
我回家的时候不想被盘问
I don't need to be grilled when I get home.
- 你知道吗 我在工作的时候已经够累了  - 被盘问
- You know, I do enough of that at work. - Grilled?
你这么想的吗
Is that what you think I'm doing?
几个小时以前
Let me just say a couple of hours ago,
我确实在弄烧烤 或者该说在用烤箱
I was indeed doing some grilling or... broiling actually,
Grill有烧烤及盘问之意
至于grill是下方加热 像平常烤肉 broil则是上方直接加热 美国烤箱有这种功能
- 为了你说过你要来的晚饭  - 哦 天哪 你想让我
- for a dinner you committed to. - Oh, my God, do you want me
把晚饭的钱给你吗
to pay you for the veggie steaks?
不 我不想
No, I don't want you to...
这不是重点
that is so beside the point.
几个月来 你一直渴望Juliette能记得你
For months, you have been dying for Juliette to remember you.
现在 她终于记得了 但你却
And now, she finally does, and you don't even...
我是说 如果我有些困惑请原谅我
I mean, forgive me if I'm a little flummoxed.
怎么 你 你不说了
What, you're... you're done talking now?
你这就 你这就去睡觉
You're just... you know, you're gonna go to bed, or...
好吧 直接走了
Oh, you're leaving.
真行 你要去哪儿
That's interesting. Where are you going?
也许你该好好关注自己的生活了
You might wanna start looking into getting your own life.
你才是该好好想想怎么把自己房子拿回来
I think you need to start looking into getting your own house.
- 哈罗  - 和我实话实说吧
- Hello? - Just be honest with me.
- Nick恨我吗  - 呃 我也不确定
- Does Nick hate me?  - I, um, don't know, actually.
我是说 他刚来过 紧接着就离开了
I mean, he just got here, and then he left.
而且他心情不太好
And he wasn't in a very good mood.
他去你那里的时候发生了什么
What happened when he came over to your place?
我做了晚餐 然后就开始聊天
I made us dinner. And then, I started talking.
突然 一切好像都变了
And then, everything just sort of fell apart.
后来他就走了
And then he just left.
也许是工作上的事情
Maybe something's going on at work.
不知道 让我打给Hank问问
I don't know. Let me call Hank.
- 我会再打给你  - 好
- I'll call you back. - Okay.
- Griffin  - 嗨 Hank 我是Monroe
- Griffin. - Hey, Hank, it's Monroe.
Nick在工作中有遇到什么事吗
Is something going on with Nick at work?
怎么了
Why?
你知道他应该去Juliette家吃晚餐吗
You know he was supposed to have dinner at Juliette's?
- 他没去吗  - 去了
- Didn't he? - No.
然后他又来过我这儿
And then he comes over here,
我问他饭吃的咋样
and I, like, asked him how it went.
他却叫我自己管好自己 然后就走了
And he tells me to get a life, and then he leaves.
听起来不像他的作风
That doesn't sound like him.
他对我是什么都没说
I mean, he hasn't said anything to me.
或许他身上发生了些我们不知道的事
I mean, maybe he's got something going on we don't know about.
让我看看我能查出点什么
Let me see what I can find out.
啥事
Yeah?
我刚回到警局
Hey, I just got back to the precinct.
- 你在哪  - Bent Brick餐厅
- Where are you? - Down at the Bent Brick.
做点儿医生不让做的事儿
Just what the doctor didn't order.
我马上到 帮我留杯啤酒
I'm on my way. Save me a beer.
你见过这个吗
You saw one of those?
啥时候
When?
- 几小时以前  - 有什么要告诉我的吗
- A few hours ago. - Something I should know about?
我不知道她是谁
I don't know what she is.
- 我认识吗  - 是那个证人
- Anybody I know? - It's the witness.
什么 Khole Sedgwick 你又回去看她了
Wait, Khloe Sedgwick? You went back and saw her again?
这太厉害了
That is awesome.
到底是谁 是个小精灵吗
Who is that? Is that, like, a little elf?
你是个漫画家吗 你有名吗
Are you a comic book artist? Are you famous?
你是个我应该知道的人吗 我觉得你肯定是
Are you someone that I should know? I bet you are.
兄弟 我女朋友对科幻类的东西很痴迷
Dude, my girlfriend freaks out about Sci-Fi stuff.
她爱死它们了 让我看看
She loves it. Let me see it...
嘿 别惹我
Hey! Leave it alone, man.
哇哦 别紧张
Whoa. I-it's fine.
我不会毁了它的
I'm not gonna hurt it.
我只是想给她看看
I'm just gonna show it to her.
她就在那里 我不会损坏你的作品的
She's right over here. It's not even gonna get damaged.
喔 喔 喔 放轻松
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Take it easy.
不要犯傻
Let's not make a mistake here.
请冷静
Now, just calm down.
我 我很冷静
I--I am calmed down.
那家伙刚刚无缘无故打我
That guy just punched me for no reason.
Nick 要不你先回家吧
Hey, Nick, why don't you just head outta here, go on home?
这里我来处理
I got this.
呃 你想让他就这样溜掉吗
Okay, what, you're just gonna let him go?
你就这样让他走了 你可是个警察啊
You let him just walk out? You're just... you're a cop.
你就应该负责抓坏人什么的
You're supposed to arrest people.
你已经有点失控了
And you've had a little bit more than you can handle.
除非你想在醉汉拘留所里呆上一晚
Unless you wanna spend a night in a drunk tank,
你还是乖乖坐下 保持安静吧
I suggest you sit down and shut up.
- 我从没见过  -我也没
- I've never seen one. - Me neither.
Nick真的为了这画在酒吧里打了人吗
Nick really hit somebody in a bar over this?
我也不敢相信
I didn't believe it, either.
我是说 那人喝醉了
I mean, the guy was drunk.
Nick让他滚开
And Nick told him to back off,
但这还是有点过分
but still, it was a little over the top.
他在这里也是 那么过分
That's the way he was here... over the top.
那如果你俩都不知道这是什么
So if neither of you know what this is,
我们怎么知道我们要对付啥东西
how do we find out what we're dealing with?
什么
What?
这就是Marie姑妈的拖车啊
So this is Aunt Marie's trailer.
嗯 就是这个
Yep. This is it.
哇
Wow.
这些可是很稀有的东西
Wow, this is some really rare stuff.
是啊 这的确有很多稀有货
Yeah, there's some pretty rare stuff in here,
但我们得先研究这些
but we need to begin with these.
这些书都在这里啊
This is where the books come from.
还有其它东西
Among other things.
这真是一个名副其实的"格林生物学"研究博物馆
Yeah, it's a veritable museum of wesen-ology,
记载着格林们捕杀我们这些人
chronicling the grimms proud tradition
的骄傲历史
of hunting and beheading people like us.
哦
Oh.
很高兴能了解这个
Nice to know.
那我们现在要找的是
So we're looking for...
长这样的人
Somebody who looks like this.
我的天 这糟透了
Oh, my God. This is awful.
- 穆赛  - 你说啥
- Musai. - What?
她就是这种
That's what she is.
对吧
Right?
- 是  - 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
都在这儿写着呢
It's right here.
不过 都是德语写的
It's all in German, of course.
听听这个 这是1888年写的
Listen to this. This was written in 1888.
"我的一位艺术家朋友 名叫Gauguin
"I was called in by an artist acquaintance of mine
"把我叫了进去
"Whose name is Gauguin.
"前一天晚上 他被他的另一个
"The night before, he had been accosted
"艺术家朋友 Van Gogh
"With a razor blade by another artist friend of his
用刀片给划伤了
"By the name of Van Gogh.
"Gauguin担心他的朋友
"Gauguin is worried that his friend is under
"被一个妓女毒害了心智
"The pernicious influence of a prostitute.
"他让我负责去打探一下
"He assigned me the task of discovering
"这位Rachel到底是何许人也
"What kind of witch this Rachel was.
"我很不爽地发现
"I was loathe to discover
"这个妓女并不是巫女兽
"That this trollop was no hexenbiest
"而是一个穆赛
"But a Musai.
"尽管她在某些时候
"And although she may have been
"是Van Gogh最大的灵感来源
"Van Gogh's greatest inspiration for some time,
但她已经开始造成负面影响"
her influence was starting to take its toll..."
"导致他切下了自己的耳朵
"Causing him to cut off his own ear.
"我还了这个人情
"I returned the favor,
"而且 我没有脱掉她的衣服
"And instead of taking off her clothes,
而是取了她的项上人头"
of course, I took off her head."
Van Gogh 哈
Van Gogh, huh?
我只是照着读而已
I mean, I'm just reading what's here.
但是
But...
呃
Um...
"穆赛的吻会让人愉悦并上瘾
"The kiss of the Musai is as euphoric and addictive
"就像麻醉药一样
"As any narcotic known to man.
"而且一旦开始 他们之间的关系
"And once begun, the relationship...
往往以疯狂 破坏 和死亡结束"
Always ends in madness, destruction, and death."
等等 等等 好吧
Hold on, hold on. Okay.
可能也没那么惨
It may not be that bad after all, yeah.
"只要她不吻对方 什么事都不会发生"
"None of this will happen as long as she hasn't kissed him."
神马
What?
我看见她亲了他的手
I saw her kiss his hand.
而且 说实话 我也不知道
And, man, who knows what happened
他今晚过去的时候发生了什么
when he went over there tonight.
顺便问一下 谁知道Nick现在在哪吗
By the way, anybody know where Nick is?
你还穿着和昨晚一样的衣服
You're in the same clothes as last night,
你回家了吗
you make it home?
那不是我家
That's not my home.
- 那你睡了吗  - 昨晚的事情有点记不清了
- You make it to bed? - Last night's a bit of a blur.
你还好吗
You all right?
只要你停止审讯我 我就挺好
I would be if you stopped interrogating me.
好吧
Fair enough.
听着 Nick 我对你昨天画的Khole
Look, Nick, I've been doing a little research
做了一些研究
on that drawing you made of Khloe.
我想我知道她是啥了
I think I found out what she is.
- 是吗 啥  - 是个穆赛
- Yeah, what? - A Musai.
那又怎样 你现在觉得你自己是个格林了吗
So what, you think you're a Grimm now?
我 呃 有东西要给你看
I've, uh, got something to show you.
昨晚发生的 队长
Happened last night. Captain.
怎么了
Yeah?
这是昨晚9点半发生的
This is from 9:30 P.M. Last night.
当警官到达现场的时候
By the time the officers responded to the alarm,
他早就离开了 不过他就是我们要找的凶手 Anton Cole
he was long gone, but it's our shooter, Anton Cole.
- 所以他还活着  - 毫无疑问
- So he's alive? - No doubt about it.
他为啥闯进油漆店呢
Why break into a paint store?
我想可能和Khloe Sedgwick有关系
Oh, I think it has something to do with Khloe Sedgwick.
- 为啥  - 哦 直觉而已
- Why? - Oh, just a hunch.
你懂的
You know what those are.
三年前的警方报告
Police report from three years ago.
一位叫Max Fisher的作曲家
Composer by the name of Max Fisher
在精神崩溃后被送进了精神病院
was committed to an asylum after a mental breakdown.
那是在他用酸液
That was after he attacked a sculptor
泼了一位雕塑家的脸之后
by throwing acid on his face.
猜猜当时谁在和他交往
Guess who he was seeing at the time?
Khloe Sedgwick
Khloe Sedgwick.
根据上面所述 她同时也在和那个雕塑家交往
And according to this, she was also dating the sculptor.
五年前的自杀案
Suicide from five years ago.
小说家 Ellis Harlan 在她的女朋友抛弃他以后
Novelist named Ellis Harlan hung himself
上吊自杀了
after his girlfriend left him.
- 那他的女朋友是  - Khloe Sedgwick
- And the girlfriend was... - Khloe Sedgwick.
看来她真有那么两把刷子
She must be quite a woman.
嘿 收到市中心的报警 说有人蓄意破坏
Hey, just got a vandalism call from downtown.
我或许知道凶手要那么多油漆做什么了
I can know what our shooter did with all that paint.
这个案子你或许想一起参与哦
You might want to join us for this one, sir.
穆赛的嘴唇能分泌一种精神物质
The Musai's lips secrete a kind of psychotropic substance
没有解药
for which there's no medicinal antidote.
神马
What?
总有解药的吧 对吗
There's gotta be something, right?
哦 等一下
Oh, wait, wait.
呃 没有
Mm. Nothing.
那咋办 传说中的死亡之吻
So what? It's the proverbial kiss of death?
强烈的欲望可能和爱相混淆
Obsessive desire can be confused with love.
不管这是什么 这不是爱
Whatever this is, it ain't love.
的确不是 但感觉上也许很像
No, but it probably feels like it.
我觉得能打破这种情感的唯一手段
I think the only way to break an obsession like this
可能是真正的爱
is with the real thing.
- Juliette  - 哦 嗨
- Juliette. - Oh, hey.
我就觉得我能在这找到你们
I was hoping I would find you here.
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's wrong?
我得回到那个拖车里
I need to go back to the trailer.
不是吧 又是拖车
Really? The trailer again?
在发生了上次的事之后
After what happened the last time,
你觉得这是个好主意
you sure that's such a good idea?
无论是好是坏 我都必须去
Good or not, I-I need to go.
好吧 呃
Okay. Um...
我们现在有点忙 但我可以
Um, we're sort of busy right now, but I could...
不
No.
- 什么不  - 我要钥匙就行了 Monroe
- No? - I just need the key, Monroe.
我得自己去
I need to go alone.
不管那晚上Nick带我去的时候发生了什么
Whatever happened the night that Nick brought me there
显然那非常重要
is clearly really important.
为了让我能理解
And in order for me to understand
现在发生了什么 我必须试着去
what's going on right now, I have to try to reconnect
想起当时发生的事
with what happened then.
她是对的 你应该让她去
She's right. You should let her.
好吧 我想
Uh, well, I think...
我应该让她去
I should let her too.
好的
Okay.
祝我好运 算了
Wish me luck, or... Whatever.
凶手可能是个神经病
Our killer might be a psychopath and all that,
我可不是什么粉丝
and I'm not saying I'm a fan or anything,
但你不得不说这家伙还挺有创意的
but you gotta give him some credit.
- Anton很厉害嘛  - 没人看见他画这个吗
- Anton's got an eye. - No one saw him do this?
- 在凌晨两点可没什么人  - 就算有人看见
- Not at 2:00 in the morning. - Well, even if they did,
波特兰也不是完全没有街头艺术嘛
street art is not exactly unheard of in Portland.
他去哪了
Where'd he go?
Nick
Nick!
- 嘿 我没法追上他  - 好吧 我去追
- Hey, I can't run him down. - Okay, I'm on it.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
Nick画的
Nick drew it.
好的 我记得你告诉过我
Okay, I remember you told me
你能做的某些事
about something you could do,
你拥有的某种能力
some kind of ability that you had.
拜托 让我记起来
Come on, memory.
我知道和这些书有关
I know it had something to do with these books,
这些
these...
来自这些
From the...
诡异 十分诡异的画里
Weird, weird drawings.
你告诉我什么来着
What did you tell me?
你说了什么来着
What did you say to me?
加把劲啊 Nick
Come on, Nick.
请帮帮我 我在努力
Please help me. I'm trying.
我真的在拚命努力
I am... I'm really trying here.
看到这些书了吗
You see these books? You see these books?
You see these books?
书里面是我的祖先所绘的图画
They're filled with drawings made by my ancestors
还有其他具有同样的能力问题的人
and others who had the same ability problem,
随便你怎么叫
whatever you wanna call it.
画上的生物是格林生物
And the drawings are of wesen,
他们喜欢这样称呼自己
which is how they like to refer to themselves.
我能看见他们
And that's what I can see,
格林也能
what the Grimms can see.
他们是存在于我们之中的物种
They're like species that exist within us.
呃 一部分人
Well, some of us.
总之 这里有狼人
Anyway, there are Blutbaden...
农夫猪
and Bauerschwein...
狐妖 和海狸怪 都在这本书里
Fuchsbaus and Eisbibers, and they're all in these books.
Juliette 说真的 我可不是在胡编乱造
Juliette, really, I am not making this up.
真的 我没骗你
Really, I am not making this up.
Griffin警探
Detective Griffin.
Hank 这是Rosalee和Monroe
Hank? It's Rosalee and Monroe.
- Nick和你在一起吗  - 没有啊
- Is Nick with you? - No.
- 我还指望他和你在一起呢  - 没 他不在警局里
- I was hoping he was with you. - No, he's not at the precinct.
Hank 听着 我们找到了更多关于穆赛的信息
Hank, listen, we found out more about the Musai.
如果她和Nick之间的联系已经建立
There's no way we can break the connection
那就没有办法断开了
between her and Nick if it's already been established,
至少我无能为力
at least not with anything I can do.
而且Nick失踪了
And Nick is in the wind.
不 他会去她所在的地方
No, he's gonna be going wherever she is.
如果他们在一起 情况只会变得更糟
And it'll only get worse if they're together.
那如果找到他们 我们该怎么做
So what do we do when we find them?
让他远离她 直到我们找出办法为止
Keep him away from her until we can figure out what to do.
- 队长  - 嗯 你找到他了
- Captain. - Yeah, you find him?
还没 是Monroe的电话
No. It's Monroe.
他认为Nick会跟随她而去
He thinks Nick will be going to her.
好的 打电话给
All right, call the officer
保护她的警员 我马上过去
protecting her house. I'm going over there.
我回头打给你
I'll call you back.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我不知道 我感觉 奇怪
I don't know. I feel... Different.
那些我所见的东西和我所记得的事情
The things that I saw and the things that I remembered...
那你记起他带你过去的
So you remembered what happened
那天晚上发生的事情了
the night he took you there?
应该是的 当时我并不相信他
I think so. I didn't believe him.
我是说 他告诉了我所有的事情 但我仍然没相信他
I mean, he told me everything, but I didn't believe him.
那现在呢
And what about now?
你相信Nick 不是吗
You believe Nick, don't you?
你也是
And so do you.
我们都相信他
We do.
呃 因为当时 我觉得他疯了
Yeah, 'cause I just... I thought he was crazy.
当你了解之后 某些看似疯狂的事情
Some things aren't as crazy as they seem
其实并没有那么疯狂
when you kind of get to know them.
我得见他
I need to see him.
我要告诉他 我相信他
I need to tell him that I believe him.
他在哪
What... where is he?
呃
Uh...
Gates警员
Officer Gates.
我是Griffin警探
This is Detective Griffin.
我估计Burkhardt警探会出现在那边
I'm expecting Detective Burkhardt to show up there.
他一旦出现就通知我
Let me know as soon as he does.
他刚从我身边走过 朝着目标的房子过去了
He just walked past me heading for the subject's house.
队长已经在路上了 不要让Burkhardt警探离开
Captain's on his way. Do not let Detective Burkhardt leave.
遵命 长官
Yes, sir.
我想要你
I need you.
你是个格林
You're a Grimm.
这无所谓
It doesn't matter.
你必须证明你自己
You have to prove it.
Anton在这里
Anton's here.
哪里
Where?
她是我的
She's mine!
我不能
I can't...
只要他活着就不行
Not as long as he's alive.
别打了
Let's go.
不 Khloe
No. Khloe...
- 长官 他已经被铐上了  - Nick
- Sir, he's handcuffed. - Nick!
- 她是我的  - 够了 别乱来
- She's mine! - Come on, that's enough!
- 我们抓到他了  - 你不能拥有她
- We got him.  - You can't have her.
你永远不会拥有她
You'll never have her!
- 永远  - 够了
- Never! - That's enough!
你觉得你能拥有她
You think you can have her?
没人能做到
No one can!
那么 长话短说 看来
So, long story short, it would seem
Nick看起来不像他平时那样
that the reason Nick hasn't been himself
对你 或者我 对我们所有人 是因为
with you or me or... or any of us is because...
呃 是因为他受到了
Well, because he's sort of been...
受到了另一个女人的影响
Under the influence of another woman.
但这 这不能算是他的错
But it's... it's not necssarily his fault.
她是 呃
She's, well...
- 她是  - 格林生物吗
- She's... - Wesen?
啥 Nick去年就试着告诉我这件事了
What? That's what Nick was trying to tell me last year.
是的
Yes.
而且我们觉得他现在可能有大麻烦了
And we think he could be in a lot of trouble right now.
这和我身上发生的事情很像吗
Is this anything like what happened to me?
是有点像
It is...
只是这次没有现成的解药
Except the antidote's not on the shelf.
那解药在哪
Where is it?
解药是你
It's you.
- 我们知道你是什么  - 真的吗
- We know what you are. - Really?
- 那我到底是什么  - 穆赛
- And what would that be? - Musai.
好吧 既然你知道这个 那你也会知道
Well, if you know that,
那不是我所能控制的
then you know that it's out of my control.
我并没有要他迷恋我
I don't ask for the attention that men give me.
看起来你也不是很想拒绝啊
You don't try very hard to refuse it.
呃 我为什么要拒绝呢 没有了我
Well, why would I? Without me,
- 他们就什么也不是  - 没有你 他们才能活命
- they would be nothing. - Without you, they'd be alive.
不管你对我的警探做了什么 都必须停止
Whatever you've done to my Detective, it's gonna stop.
我无能为力 我生来就是这样
Well, I can't help it. I was born this way.
你看 你警探的真正问题
You see, the real problem
在于他是个格林
with your Detective is that he's a Grimm.
一切都因为他的身份而发展的更加迅速
And it's all happening much faster because of who he is.
Nick拥有我从没体验过的能量
Nick has more power than I've ever experienced,
而我和他很般配
and I'm good for him.
你必须立刻停止这一切
You're gonna stop this right now.
我从没学会如何停止
I've never known how to stop it.
长官 你之前说嫌犯被收押的时候要通知你
Sir, you wanted to know when the suspect had been booked?
他现在就在牢房里
He's in his cell.
我不能
I can't...
只要他活着就不行
Not as long as he's alive.
你必须证明你自己
You have to prove it.
Anton在这里
Anton's here.
她没有给我们太多选择
She didn't give us many options.
是啊 是啊 有一件事可以肯定
Yeah, yeah, one thing's for sure:
我们不能让他接近她
We can't let her anywhere near him.
哦 那我们怎么做 把他锁起来吗
Oh, what do we do? Lock him up?
必要时可以 他现在在哪
If we have to. Where is he now?
嘿 看这个
Hey, look at this.
嘿
Hey.
有人知道Nick在哪里吗
Anybody know where Nick is?
在你内心深处
There's something that's just
有一股强大的力量
deeply powerful about you.
这种力量无法被控制
It's not something that can be controlled.
- Nick 不要  - 我不能
- Don't! Nick...  - I can't.
Nick 你要是开枪那我可罩不住你了
Nick, I can't protect you from this.
- Nick 停下 请听我说  - 只要他活着就不行
- Nick, stop. Please listen.  - Not as long as he's alive.
- Juliette 在这里  - 你怕了吗
- Juliette is here.  - Does that scare you?
看着我
Look at me.
我对眼光独特的人有感觉
I have a thing for people who see the world differently.
想想你现在在做什么
Think about what you're doing.
嗯 很多伟大的艺术家都英年早逝
Mm, a lot of the great artists died young
而且有暴力倾向 近乎疯狂
and violently, half-mad.
但我不认为他们之中的任何人会愿意
But I doubt that any of them would trade their fame
用他们的盛名换取完整而乏味的一生
for banality and a longer life.
请看着我
Please just look at me.
我从没强迫过别人
I never force myself on them.
我启发他们
I inspire them.
Nick 看着我
Nick, look at me!
- 呃啊  - 睁开眼睛
- Uhh! - Open your eyes.
你得看着我 Nick 睁开眼睛
You have to see me, Nick. Open your eyes.
Juliette
Juliette.
是我
Yeah.
你在这里干啥
What are you doing here?
我是为你而来 正如你曾经陪着我一样
I'm here for you, just like you were there for me.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还想干啥
Really?
好吧 今天算你走运
Well, this is your lucky day.
我会放了你
I'm gonna let you walk.
你一旦出去
And when you do,
就得远离波特兰 并且永远不准回来
you're gonna leave Portland and never come back.
因为如果你回来了
Because if you do,
我的另一面可不是个警察
there's a part of me that doesn't wear a badge.
而且谁都不知道他会做出什么事
And there's no telling what he'll do.
== 格林 第二季第20集 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献
== 翻译&时间轴：暮暮 特特 校对：天之行者 蜜蜜==
== 统筹：尧之雪 后期：飞在果壳里 封装：天之行者 ==
本字幕仅用于学习交流之用
禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
【H-SGDK】字幕组欢迎各位加入
有意者请加QQ群109164858，注明 字幕组+申请职位即可
== 格林 第二季第20集 完 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献